so if you go to autismspeaks.org
with autism for the very first time like
it's not something that you could just
simply do like just on your own right
but you want to say oh I didn't have the
$10,000 to do it no I have not been
clinically diagnosed by a doctor because
I'm not paying $10,000 to do that and
most people will tell you that at this
age you don't need a clinical diagnosis
in the in that sense if you're broke
just say that
right but even if you did in fact have
that right and you didn't even take the
steps whether it's through health
insurance or the $10,000 to try to like
go further because it's not even just
about the diagnosis cuz if you were
really searching for answers and you
find something that explains something
for you right if you wanted to change it
or if you want to be better about it you
would go to a clinician who can come up
with a plan give you some tools or
whatever to be better about it